[Music]
hi everybody
I'm taking it over to the show right now
we did press and it took a long time
right now we did press and it took a
long time and also I'm hungry so if any
all have food I'd appreciate it ah yo
what up so look here's here's my badge
going to the show right now ban that
user done sup how do i how do i
permanently hide user or even better
perfect big-time CES calm a takeover
it's true it's true so you know y'all
gonna y'all gotta wait while we while we
get to the show your streams is so funny
Thank You oh yeah yeah yeah we're we're
launching the Hyundai harness yeah
that's that's a product announcement
yeah we're making an announcement it's
gonna take some time it's not a
self-driving over no no it's not no you
didn't miss anything don't worry you
ever watch The Bachelor
hey virtually Chris you ever watch The
Bachelor where you gotta like wait
through seven commercial breaks before
they tell you who they're giving the
final rose to we're gonna make this like
that so we're gonna wait for the people
to show up everywhere my my comma
jumpsuit right now CES is the Consumer
Electronics Show it is the largest the
largest trade show in the world and I'm
here right now on location in Vegas and
we wait for some people to show up
what's up Larry a role player carve a
jumpsuit does anyone want to buy one of
these I'll sell you mine it's mine
personally they give them to the company
I'll sell you my person
what's up yes I heard Sony made a card
no open pilots a boy it's not allowed
you purchased the Kama jumpsuit well
well well look into that we'll look into
that
no I'm not signing anything yo I'm
really hungry or if you guys got pizza
I really I really want some pizza if
we're announcing a camera extension or a
micro sized yawn hmm you can buy my
t-shirt right now go to comment on AI
this Burger King y'all I'll settle for a
burger you got tender-crisp that'd be
great
um but no mail on that tender-crisp
spicy tender crisp good toe
it was a spoiler it's not time yet or
Carver and I think when I win a Ford
Flex ride no open pilots support yet
yeah full self-driving yeah yeah that's
guys it's not real test the lie to you
yeah bobland I'm gonna feel you um yeah
no full-size wrapping is not real Johnny
Stein welcome welcome to the first time
stream bro no but you're gonna you're
gonna come with me right now well we
went make our way to the common both I'm
Tesla didn't lie they exaggerated you
know they stretched the truth full
self-driving won't be real for quite a
while but we have an incredible
announcement planned for you today I
didn't put any steel balls to try to
throw through the new product
unfortunately what time right I lied are
you guys are gonna really Tesla
stretched that your full self Driving's
not coming anytime soon
I look tired yeah I'm doing press all
morning it's called marking again we
don't do that
dude can't believe commas fine oh yeah
there's new product oh well you guys
don't know there's a new product what
are we here for
want to think about the ps5 and wheels I
saw the logo I don't know if anything
else was announced yeah open palette is
quite good right cock vapor will know
this product is real and I'll tell you
this I'll do a leak right now I'll let
you guys know that you'll be able to
purchase this product literally as soon
as this live stream is over
cool yeah can you jump out right here
thank you very much have a good day
yes I'm in an uber right now uh welcome
to CES good thing I remembered my badge
George Hotz
I present no we don't have any events in
South Florida I'm sorry all right we're
heading in right now all right I'm not
sure I'm allowed to livestream in there
so I'm keeping you guys on the DL no I'm
gonna I'm gonna bring you guys in just
just be stealthy like right I promise
you it's not a connector
thank you all right we just we just got
by security
I could put you guys in my pocket if we
need to but I don't think we need to
oh is this a line no it can't be it
can't be all right we're going in we're
going in I'm gonna flip you around oh
yeah we're going in all right live from
the CES showroom floor I'm glad you love
the Subaru harness we're announcing that
car no no no we're in we're in we're in
oh no you're gonna have to wait for the
news all right what do we got is it
quality good I've got a good stream
going y'all cooking it up in a crock-pot
Tyler thank you welcome welcome to the
live stream haha good we're in
autonomous drives generation the next
generation millimeter wave radar guys yo
okay quality that's good this is not
shot on a lake oh look 403 um now I'm a
little sick Twila tired too are we lost
where's our booth that
oh yeah IOT infrastructure oh yeah
yo yo alright everybody hide the new
product stand in front of it don't let
anybody see the new product yet stand in
front of it
welcome to the calm a icees booth I'm
glad to have you all here with us oh yo
on the press demo this morning the only
disengagement there was an accident
right in front of us
yeah like this car swerved across two
lanes so I disengaged for safety
definitely not caused by Karma alright
welcome what time is it oh it's 58 oh we
gotta at least make them wait does our
neighbors on say uh-huh yeah
we good to put the website line all
right
well but we'll get we'll give the word
what your biggest fan you want to be on
the live stream
hi I'm George nice to meet you hi George
yes yeah the whole audience here we got
317 people live right here right now in
the kombu 'the we got that PVC from the
highest quality strip club in Vegas oh
wait okay they can't see that that would
be the product oh that would be oh oh
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa well that was
close that was close
combo lasers come a phone does everyone
want to introduce themselves
all right so um we're gonna let you know
who gets the Rose we're just gonna make
everybody wait like five minutes let's
let's let's launch their product no no
and 352 virtual view is on blocking the
mic uh sound okay the audio is weird
when I flip the phone flip the front cam
otherwise audio is low oh I see okay
what's the front cam we're right here in
the comic I see yes booth I've seen
Logan Paul do the shot before no Harold
is driving the Prius right now 4 p.m.
yeah we're gonna oh man
yeah don't don't let him don't let him
throw let him see anything oh yourself
you know Alex let's go let's go oh it's
one o'clock no I'm not on coke I did
take two dayquil this morning though
well well we don't talk about that yeah
yeah yo what kind of video is this no
it's - I don't drink caffeine anymore
I'm off drugs guys I'm off drugs clean
20 20 shut out to our users yeah this is
a hobble spirit video it's a nice video
yeah showing off your videos 403
watching 409 whoa and toenails how did
you how did you see the name of the
product did you see the name of the
product right here yo check them out
check them out the name is revealed
it is the comma to
we got boxes there's a lot of them and
we still get a little bit of time we're
gonna do the real unveiling of the
product just got away for a few more
people to get in here we got to get to
at least 420 that's right
we need more people than Tesla's share
price come on let's go let's go , - the
video came out before the livestream
announced defconn is on the store guys
everything you see here today is live
right away
it's shipping on the 20th so if you like
what you see get your credit card out
right now get your credit card out right
now see this your credit cut out right
now I leaked the number nope Amex is the
number on the back no it does don't work
all right all right maybe we can slowly
start trickling things out oh no that's
that's too much that's that's not
trickling yeah yeah have you guys seen
this here's a harness
alright 4:30 are we still getting people
though we got away we got away is the
website live it is a live website live o
do it do it wait wait it's live dog Oh
people are slamming it is it going down
slow to load all right guys if the
websites live this is the comma to check
it out truly beautiful hardware remember
some of you we reached out to and we
asked a bunch of times if you were
making the EON what would you make and
that is exactly what we've done here
with the camuto so Paul we already sold
one yo that was so fast this one's off
right here okay so what phone it's a
custom phone
I mean it's custom phone because it
doesn't have a battery it has an
infrared camera it has a custom fan
cooling solution that you're never gonna
hear and it has driver monitoring 24/7
with the infrared cameras right here
it's based on a l'école X 720 but up Oh
just ordered this is it's 999 dollars
this is the comma - it comes in a
beautiful box so these boxes have real
foamies in them yes oh let's open a box
up let's let's put let's put a comma -
here
wait what's wrong that one you brought
the broken phones ah no no no this knows
what's good we're good we're good we
good we good but oh yeah
let's just let's well hold flip the
camera around the comet - oh this is
backwards the foams in backwards
lift it out it's gonna go up it around
don't worry all the comet tools will be
packed properly yo look at this we got
we got a bit of an audience here for
really comas most consumer friendly
product yet welcome to the fleet we have
a beautiful grab your phone to get
started oh it doesn't need a speaker we
figured out how to make the sounds mad
loud the comma - is really designed for
acoustics check it out
in the bottom you'll find a harness it's
the same harness oh yeah
the pandas built-in I almost forgot to
tell you this is an ODBC connector so
that will just plug right into your car
you don't need anything else all you
need is a comma - and a car harness so
this car harness just use an ODB to see
cable process is the same Snapdragon 820
one it's compatible to Aeon software but
you get driver monitoring 24/7 yeah it's
running on 50.7 release here are
supported cars same ones as before oh no
oh no not the same GoPro mount do we
have a mount
we don't have mount let's get a mount oh
yeah we redid the mount - of course you
think we'd leave that crappy GoPro mount
we invented the double-wide GoPro the
comment you will not comment uses way
less power because it doesn't have to
charge the battery constantly these are
the mounts custom cut VHB we invented
the double wide go problem yeah if they
already have a harness you can just buy
it you don't have to buy another harness
what you can tell them what you want on
your sold five y'all wow this is a lot
can you sell your black panda not to us
yeah you can sell it short same comma
power so if you buy a harness it comes
all in this one beautiful box this box
is what's gonna show up on your doorstep
ha IR LEDs dual IR LEDs
camera in here you know the you know
board you guys been hyped about in here
is an you know it's a Snapdragon 820 one
face ID built in four DM it's not have a
face ID I'm not sure what that would do
but it has a camera right here and
that's for place we replace the one
that's usually in the phone with an
infrared camera Uno is the panda that's
integrated into the comma to what is the
you know so it's the built in panda so
you no longer need a panda the install
in the car is completely stealth no more
stuff on your windshield oh did I not
tell you this has a built in
high-precision GPS in fact inside let me
just pull this off inside of this
antenna of this mount you'll find a GPS
antenna built in this has the same high
precision GPS as a grey panda and a
black panda all built in is there a wire
lens it's slightly wider I think it's a
few degrees wider we have no problems
seeing you bought yours a month ago
pandas are now extinct yeah tear down
and reveal I mean you'll have to buy one
panda Eon GPS all built into the comet
to the case is made of ABS if you have
weird windshield angles it should be
fine I mean guys it's the eon but good
uno will not be open-source seven years
early will get years early absolutely
same harnesses
and it's just that same ODBC connector
you're just gonna need one wire and it
plugs in right there you can also use
that as a USB to connect to the phone
no you won't have to take the common two
out of your car on hot days the comma
two can withstand up to 85 degrees
Celsius we tested it we put it in an
oven it'll withstand any heat your car
has to throw at it and that's because it
has no battery in fact the battery has
been replaced by a thermal pan given the
coma - unprecedented thermals oh we
didn't we should have brought a few that
were kind of in oh yeah yeah um if you
have an outstanding Aeon order just
email support we'll cancel that for you
because you know you want that comment
to all the power of an Australian summer
does not get up to 85 degrees Celsius
that's very hot they could probably do
more than 85 as well
yeah that's what the rating is on the
comment Oh typical for consumer
electronics all right that took a lot of
out of me and everything yeah it took a
lot
oh we have beautiful pictures yeah well
okay we're zooming out on the booth you
can see the full booth now it's almost
the same price it's 999 dollars for the
combi - oh and what we didn't tell you
is that the comma - includes three three
months of comma Prime every comma - is
gonna ship with a SIM card reactivate it
if you buy it in the US and you just
need to go in the app and you get three
free months of comma Prime we've updated
the software so the the drives upload in
real time using comma Prime
you'll be able to get updates using that
free comma Prime for three months so if
you purchase an eon two weeks ago yeah
absolutely
we have a 30-day return policy so if you
have any on that you bought in the last
30 days you're welcome to send it back
lane changes coming in the next release
boot times about the same as an eon but
you don't really need to turn it off no
battery no power draw it's pretty low
and we're gonna work on bringing the the
power draw while the car is off down
even more there will not be a Raspberry
Pi 4 version just a weak little thing
there's opie drive better with the new
Aeon there's some things that are better
about it
so the thermals are a lot better on it
your CPUs a lot less likely to trip the
throttle out you still need the obd2
connection but that just uses the power
which connects to the Panda same cameras
except IR so you guys can do DM at night
um
boot time is all the software question
we can bring down boot time and power
draw down with software updates and we
will continue to do that we're at booth
25 20 can I show you a boot show you my
shoe no never mind I can't have their
own camera selected Ricardo give
anything to add
at night
oh wait you guys know it's they say you
can't hear you guys can't hear anyone
for George yeah yeah maybe yeah you can
only hear this yeah so big improvements
I mean George only went through it but
fundraising through that so no more fun
at sticking out of the product just one
why are going inside the stock camera
the other phoebe's driver my tonight
there is is being shown in the video so
that money talked 24/7 and bigger mount
a GoPro
it's great yes yeah you you you really
want it you should buy one okay I was
saying that we said you guys annoying
emails asking what what did you want why
did you stop using this product and then
you answered and them really all right
how can we make this with all of the
things that they asked and that's what
we did check out the website if you
haven't brand-new website
it gets really beautiful
oh yeah and you can buy it with a firm I
know I said I'd never do that but we're
selling out cuz we got to make money
how long does it last without direct
power no time at all does another
battery is there a way to invest sadly
now we're a private company a wide-angle
camera same angle in fact you know we're
not even using the full angle of the
camera in the model so we'll get there
it's so as the harness but again
everything goes either under the trim or
is the device it's just one wire it's
the same harness so if you already have
a harness you can just use the harness
bone and harm the screen not really yeah
look at the beautiful video right remote
Java position we have no Java and we
have no remote we are hiring it's true
if you want to be hired for machine
learning to the programming challenge if
you want to be hired by open PI out
submit ports no poor quest on power
focused on pal yeah so we're gonna get
hired well I told you the program
challenge stuff no the Black Panthers
will continue to be on sale you can
upgrade your young with a black pant at
any time how many drivers are currently
on the road we have but a thousand daily
activists about 1500 monthly actives
will it work on GM absolutely do you
need to Siesta gree to get hired I don't
care who knows the new boy dad isn't
gonna do yeah yeah
you have an e on what's the USP driver
monitoring at night
big mount quiet fan it's just better
oh yeah leave it on your windshield no
battery what if you don't already have a
harness two hundred dollars you can buy
a harness firm install what phone is
it's the same phone it's a it's the same
way you go appropriate no flex Rea
living you unplugged in battery drain is
better with the new product and we're
gonna work to drive it down even further
so because there's no battery so we're
directly driving the battery circuit in
the phone which means you don't have to
go through the next step of conversion
so it's a bit more efficient and we
talked about it last night we can even
get it down even more
so yeah the comma to is gonna draw
considerably less than a neon if you're
just out of 30 days 30 days is our
policy upgrade kit no upgrade kit
Pacific batteries trash yeah oh look
yeah yeah driver monitoring at night the
old Yun will continue to be supported
through probably just shy of open pile
at one point out you fixed everything
that was not nice with the old II I'm
very nice product thank you thank you we
try
when's the press release going out we
did some press this morning and write a
medium post I was lazy alright a medium
post come a watt I don't know what the
comma watt is Robert you have anything
you want ad that's it yeah that's it
that's a new problem that's it that's
the new product I don't know I mean
these we still got a lot of people here
we got to keep the light room going how
many of you sold all I have been Oh Evan
that's a lot we're rich what do you miss
around driver monitoring it's 24/7
unique selling point I got you it's 24/7
driver monitoring works all the time can
you just run an external power source
without the ODB it's pretty clean but if
you really don't want to run it yeah
though you actually know it also
connects to the can down there - yeah
in-depth QA check out the new website
you know we've answered a lot of
questions on the website I'm gonna put
you right here hopefully you guys hear
me
driver motor isn't a selling point it is
because the alternative is we lag how
many can we sell for the first 300 ship
on the 20th of January so if you buy
within the first 300 your 20th of
January later than that it's first-come
first-serve we're gonna build them out
slow what is key is supported here yeah
we support Kia bro you know what that
says this is key
see I our work through sunglasses no it
can't see your eyes if you're wearing
sunglasses at night it will but I don't
know why you're wearing sunglasses at
night so I don't know how to help you
with that there better be an out
background unless yeah we'll get the out
back
yeah diem works kind of fine with
sunglasses it shouldn't bother you yes
but the battery was only a net negative
on your power no you don't have to
waiver that you under both the Aeon
stays on if you haven't driven your car
within 30 hours you have to wait for it
to boot but it has the same technology
as the black panda so it's not like you
have to restart your car ever you're
never gonna see any warning lights on
your dashboard all you need is a comma -
and a car honest 1199 total but will
comma 3 get released you know every year
bro it's every year bro oh where maybe
every two years I'll probably keep next
year we'll do like the comma to slam you
know what it was what do they all do
please continue to say awesome always
try thank you thank you
ah well I visit a emoto's booth here
maybe we'll do some live streaming visit
people's boots I are only on and not yes
you have plenty of light during the day
you the cover to the harness and power
the powers included with the harness so
if you're despite karma - and a harness
it's called the comma - dev kit why was
the old battery never removed from the
old deal and you had to wait for the new
product by a comma to
you can't sell just the case the phone
is completely reworked we have a custom
flex PCB inside the phone replacing the
battery we replace the camera with an IR
camera yeah the camera IG's yeah that's
right that's right I get the Alpha
reference graphics and sound yeah how
are sales go how many we sell so still
11 Oh shop link on Twitter merch Lincoln
bio oh yeah no one's bought with a firm
yet if the comment who dies from leaving
it out of the Sun is there any kind of
warranty so we have a one-year warranty
on the device so yeah if it it shouldn't
break from leaving in the Sun yeah we'll
fix it ships January 20th we got we got
a firm order we got our first two firm
order that means 12
you knew you made the right move by
waiting some time waiting pays off this
is gonna be around for a long time this
is really 1.0 hardware can we use driver
motoring all the time you can change it
to do that how many users nowadays it's
like a thousand dailies 1500 monthlies
features have come to give a coupon now
get out of here with your coupon
features of the combat oh we got a big
mount check it out it's a big solid
mount we got odbc with an integrated
panda we got IR LEDs and an IR camera a
driver monitoring night you guys can see
one on one it's on runs the same
software what feature would make one put
another hardware I think this is 1.0
hardware the software is gonna need a
bit more work how long will you gonna be
supported yeah we'll see see if it gets
annoying I mean you know it's all
hardware right well we'll phase them out
gradually but you know we are consumer
electronics company this is what we do I
am sitting on the floor yeah even though
I have an installment Union you did
purchase a common prime so how do i
repair the new combo - I'll know what
that means
steering mods I mean we didn't release
any steering rods but check discord bro
how does upgrading work for 30 day
policy that's from what is it from the
day you from the day you received it so
from the day you received it you have 30
days to return it YouTube thinks of the
karma to videos targets were children
excellent we love making child-friendly
content here at calm a I this is a
Christian channel you can have one of
these one of these can be yours if you
pick one up in person no we're not doing
in person that allowed to sell things
here he and Nero go to just comment at
AI and you can check how to update the
comma to do a new version automatic
updates over Wi-Fi or if you have comma
crime of course comma Prime no trading
program planned
Andrew hints thank you thank you
it's it's really pleasant to just leave
it in the car what's the biggest point
behind no battery because the batteries
are terrible and get puffy is
right-hand-drive supported that's all a
software problem
yep it will be all engineering is these
work these were designed and
manufactured in California that's
America for fur fur for people watching
like that that's America why did you
spend four dollars in black pant I mean
you have a black pant it's a great
product remember also that you it's 200
G per on your comma to because you don't
need to buy a harness you can reuse the
same artists that you have with your
black panda we wanted to offer an
upgrade path for eons but then we add
all these sick features to the comet to
so you're gonna want it if you use the
black man for something else absolutely
you use whatever you want
ah what's the second-best feature on the
comet to over the year on the driver
monitoring the driver monitoring 24/7 if
you're afraid you might fall asleep at
night get a comment oh because they're
trying to make money in lie to you I
would never lie to you I always tell you
the truth the whole truth nothing but
the truth
harvest the parts build a franca karma
joke
Christianity Christian channel Christian
channel bros oh yeah how many myself is
it more you boy you're mid-december yeah
you can return urea and get a
complicated I was like well still 12
what are we getting Maps I don't know
what about talent points they exist are
we adding more cameras radars and lied
ours
no lied ours lighters are stupid we can
go on the lighter is stupid to her
around CES yeah what new hundred we're
never gonna tell you in advance there's
gonna be new hardware no company does
that you can't pay for the comment with
your common points you need a different
angle mount will release the mouse stuff
open records car accidents absolutely
every feature you can want no but level
two is a spectrum level two is a
spectrum that ranges from TSS P on the
old Toyota's all the way up to open
pilot 1k a harness isn't included no
that's the brakes folks that's the it's
999 the harness is $200 more can you
recycle the black pan to hardware I mean
you can sell it what about the level for
potential company your tweeted it don't
take everything I say seriously navigate
on open pilot yeah and not anytime soon
so I think the Chinese will come with a
knockoff product yeah but it won't be as
good these are actually a lot harder to
build the deals because you have to take
the phone apart remove the battery
change the camera we have a custom flex
PCB in the phone that replaces the
battery dashcam integration has a built
in dash cam it's pretty good it's in the
app now it's actually usable now as a
dash cam I can't believe how responsive
Nick and support is to my emails
I'm getting thrown as quick as I can but
the Wi-Fi is slow here so I am getting
back to everybody to wear it Noah he was
serious his actually I think was gobbler
yeah
13 plus orders any need for faster CPU
or GPU we're still a long ways so well
oh the other thing that makes the comma
to better than the Aeon so remember with
me shipped big model on the e on and the
young kind of crapped out that was
because the eon was hitting its thermal
limits the comma to has much higher
thermal limits than the eon you can push
that chip a long ways if you don't have
thermal you know we under clock the cpu
to deal with thermal and on the comet to
we can think about about clocking it
again
a watt phone it's a lex 720 is it a
hundred percent self driving that's not
real brow fit wish your car was
supported me too it's becoming less and
less of a phone now how can you bring
mobile uploads back maybe maybe I'll
think about that what brand of fan any
one of the brand of fan
brother it's
in China somewhere um they're really
nice fans though they have they have
they have four wires to for power one
for pulse input and then we have also a
tachometer so unlike the EON we can
measure you can measure from the
software how fast the fan is turning
we'll never be better than autopilot
I wouldn't wouldn't say that harness for
GM we don't have it yet future RGB
support I don't know what that means
you're brand new explain it to me like a
five-year-old buy one of these read the
website benefits of the firmware what
firmware traffic light detection and I
don't know what I have GTT means if this
than that
Oh in savings kill people future
external cameras no Mazda support maybe
no more cameras fan is dead silent will
your job at your Sony car not for me
ship to Malaysia yes we ship worldwide
open pilot is smoother for me than
autopilot see that's what I'm saying
don't count us out of the combi two has
no battery and no mobile uploads
oh no no so just because it has no
battery it connects into your car gets
constant power from your car yawns are
still you know the stolen story yeah
yawns are still available to store same
price nothing changed
can you just connect the Prius TSU you
can you're going to need to enable
that's community feature and be aware
that does disable your autonomous
emergency braking will I sell to test
that for 10 billion yeah absolutely
wanna give you ten billion dollars I'd
do anything for not anything but yeah
10 billion 10 billion is the price where
you know you just say yes but smaller
amounts money you gotta have integrity
right for small about somebody have
integrity for 10 billion say yes
can you send a fake email that you're
replacing yard for free for my wife
we're on it see this is a Christian
Channel I do find that humorous though
is it based on a OSP could I root it
yeah the stuff to build the androids all
open-source
you can change it it's already routed
you can SSH into it if you have common
problem you can SSH into it from
anywhere what car should I buy
I want to Priya
that's a pretty good choice I check out
go-to compatible cars on the website the
Corollas bet at our choice I'm gonna
torque mounted civics real nice
no no no it's I'm making fun of
PewDiePie with the Christian Channel
thing a lot of track to meet our unicorn
goal I don't know what do you think our
valuation is we don't raise the money
again because we're gonna be profitable
because you guys are gonna buy so many
common tools the EON is missing on the
shop overview page and there's no link
for this is not it's only like the Deaf
shop ok the least over say we'll put it
in the Deaf shop grey panda
compatibility so this is a built-in
great Panda this has a built-in GPS and
one of the beautiful things about this
is finally and I know you guys always
ask and it did start to become a problem
the GPS antenna is a fixed distance from
the camera now so we know if you have a
comet - exactly where your antennas
replaced with respect to your camera
which is really nice
can you get a special edition comic - we
weren't thinking about making green ones
in honor of the Fallen comma one future
Kia Hyundai Genesis they should be how
do you hook it up to your 17 volts I
don't know how people are doing the
volts to be honest this is the black
velvet - comes in L color any color you
want except if you want something that's
not black because it's only black so you
should buy one cyber security
innovations I don't know what that means
free t-shirt with otter no free t-shirts
I'm sorry about that oh yeah I like that
yeah we'll do a hoodie at a random order
or two hoodies random order yeah that
sounds nice yeah cuz we never have to do
it cuz nobody old no no I will make sure
to actually do it I would lie to you
guys
Christian channel postive you're the one
who gets it that's right hoodies are
real volt is very hard now good luck
roll the diver hoodie we will roll the
dice it's really printed but the 3d
printing is becoming nice yeah yeah
tell them Alex we shop today if I won
someone will get a hoodie in there by
today get ot will tweet that civics
better the Prius in terms of steering
motor Oh 12 I get a hoodie a DM for
right now drive country it's a software
issue it's actually already in read the
code in monitoring D you can just
comment it out it should work yeah just
bought one year so I'm talking about
volt is super reliable a seven point one
will come out
so these ship on the 20th and we have to
ship 7.1 beforehand
resellers yeah if you want to so what we
do for resellers is we have bulk water
pricing so if you want to buy like 10
comma 2 is contact us will give you a
good price if you create a customer on
board its bootloader unlocks you
absolutely everything is unlocked what
else we got what else we got oh man I'm
losing my voice
- I've had a cold it took to day quills
this morning really dries you out I
don't want to slice of pizza so bad
right now thank you
can you make harness inside yon - it's a
difficult to fit it that's problem oh
you got me on chicken where Oh sick I'm
gonna eat orange chicken on stream
mukbang mukbang virtually Chris yeah
those are some good insulation videos
virtually Chris made the installation
videos orange oh this is the most
conference e food I've ever seen take a
look at that oh yeah conference salmon
oh the wobbles much less with big mouth
it's put free driving to ones 1.0 comes
out what's it
convergently Claire's a free one
virtually chris has had a comma - for a
while oh yeah
I love eating bye-bye simulators good
comma powers required on all cars yeah
thank you thank you
[Music]
food oh yeah yeah we're gonna get one
fast super combo model super combo model
in zero seven one lane change in zero
seven one exclusive on the comet - and
also the Aeon shout-out to virtually
Chris make me coming to videos super
impressed wait
200 miles watt no no we're not giving
away free climate 200 you can make a
video but we love videos but the old
free climate twos there's an exit in
change my ways no no don't change
highways that's the road
no freak sama twos no precognitives but
we will give a free hoodie to one person
who are expecting
how much you make from a firm we lose a
little bit on it for so what is the
comment to happen to be with the hoodie
any plans for automatic lane changes
yeah you'll see it I mean it's not
automatic its assistant yes it comes to
a complete stop in poopy traffic and
resumes depending on your car but most
of them yes one of the orders Wow 20
orders 20 and we'll BMW get from a I
[Music]
guessed 54
hmm if they buy a hoodie do they get a
free comma - no
oh the cg6 mistake it was a mistake we
learned a lot from that we little often
supercruise eating the stream people are
dropping off they don't want to see me
eat how do you determine speed from
video wouldn't you like to know when
will we move aqua highway mo I'm not
sure I think there are bloated
organization will by the Yandex team
know what AOSP is open-source all our
Android is open source as well
any details on know
come to this beautiful box
I don't know about the machspeed oh yeah
I'll spin the box
custom foam go around zs boobs and judge
big TVs Tyler will do a seat yesterday
but now right now I'm tired and a
bungling at CES dream later absolutely
yo you know what's here that's crazy
life-sized droves
alex has hat is crazy Alex wanted more
comments from you guys on the on the
stream brevin says either lives busy
just bought please include hoody in
order six-four six-five where's Andy
Andy's in Boston
vendors are fingerprinting problem is
supported on comma 2 and black Panda and
will be coming soon I think it's a lot
better than stock ACC who's on your
board me and that's it
you never give up control your company's
kids because they'll sell them out to
Wall Street I'm eating chicken pie from
America should you get black pan if you
gotta come in - no if you gonna come -
you don't need a black panda built in
its built-in there's a panda built in
their custom engineer great engineering
well dealerships offer dealerships are
welcome to we have a great discount
November of last year 30 days is the
policy 30 days is the policy I mean this
Apple let you return if you bought the
previous iPhone before the new iPhone
comes out they love till your customer
demographics I don't know them just
bought let's go it's what I like to hear
guys stop being so cheap you know what
guys I'm gonna be honest with you if the
comma - doesn't make this company
profitable no more common AI so y'all
gotta buy them no pressure
I wouldn't do that but that's true but
you know I wouldn't do that this was how
I feel its food America's profitable
though if we sell the same number of
eons that were selling comma twos I mean
if you would buy neon why would you not
buy a comma - it's literally the eon but
with all the bugs fetched it seriously
1.0 hard right yeah I'm very happy with
that this is a good product thank you
Alex wants me to remind you we're
shipping on the 20th of January I'll get
your order and soon because if you
missed the first 300 it might be a
little bit before your ships
you just bought a 400 all black panda
what so it's really only $200 right 200
is the harness you can reuse the harness
from the black panda to the EON I'm Duke
on it - I mean when not looking for UX
designers we're open power engineer
research engine how long have we been
testing it a couple months now I think
we started and we got the first ones in
November
you got these with your owner now you
have to wait longer for shipping and not
sleeping while driving how much can you
earning Commission's we don't have
independent sales reps we don't have
commissions if you want to do that you
want to buy ten I think we give you like
15% off of you buy ten so by 10 cell I'm
at 15% infrastructure DevOps sre that
might be the open pilot role um if
you're interested go request open pilot
last six months bought it yon white
panda black bear not sure you can
justify buying - it's not for everybody
it's not for everybody
look the Aeons gonna eat all of open
fire on 0.7 you're still gonna get I
think you'll get 0.8 as well you
probably even get 0.9 1.0 is probably
only for the comet tail
how did fresco pretty well yo we were
driving this morning and the only just
engagement we had on the route was an
accident that happened right in front of
us I know like this guy just like zipped
across two lanes and actually the thing
probably would have done the right thing
but I didn't want to find out comet -
will support one point out yes the
DePalma - will definitely support an
open pilot one point out tell you what
yeah Alex do what you want to tell them
you want to hold em so I can eat for a
minute yeah we're happy to do kress tell
your favorite YouTube streamers and tech
reviewers but they should review the
comma 2 is about that we might have room
for another demo while we're here so let
us know Chris Andrew furiously working
built the website Nick's been amazing
building the comet ears it's got a lot
of time building to come it too so
hopefully everybody likes it we're gonna
post a post a picture on Twitter so you
can see all 300 of them sitting in the
office they were amazing team has been
working around the clock to build the
comet oohs very excited to share them
with you guys there they look amazing in
the car
yeah if you bought within the last 30
days just send us an email
Greg's not here Greg at Georgia cancel
your order new me
I know we missed you hi Greg Morgan
George about a jerk he's so hungry man
those rice all right we have 382 viewers
anyone have any questions send one to
Linus tweet at him where does one get a
black panda the black pendant is on the
comic the car harness page
well panda be upgraded with EP 32 ever
how many hours in workday it's been
non-stop 1260 when is George talk George
talks all the time we're gonna do some
more live streams from the floor George
will take you guys around and show you
show you see yes you can see we're back
here at booth 25 20 if you're in Vegas
come by I'm trying to convince George to
maybe drop some comma twos off on the
drive home no the software is not ready
pama tube in zero seven one will be out
by the time
just on the 20th show us a full-size
Android any plans stopper money no
there's a second market for these if you
want to sell your comment beyond and buy
a comment to you
even Apple partners with somebody woulda
trained us maybe somebody should buy up
all the Youngs for cheaper and then they
didn't resell them in like Africa where
nobody knows about the combat Oh any
other questions
thanks guys just 374 people still
watching it have any questions for the
team was 0 7 1 leak them one do you guys
talk about what happened did you talk
about they know about the super combo
any other questions
what cars for the demo specific and the
case be 50 why would you know it can be
put its model that combines all the sub
modules that we had in the past together
so we have you have the driving model
the calculation model all combined into
ones and yeah it's more powerful more
than you like it
B&W support its its own flag so it's not
linear for your day we're thinking about
you you're in our minds
the same way ynw Mele had murder on his
mind oh that's the point where for kids
it's kids friendly contact comma twos
are for everybody with the driver's
license so now our epilogue at CES I
sure hope they didn't spend their
seedinvest money on that is that playing
for new merch shop Alex you guys if you
buy out all these new merch if you buy
all the comma twos we'll get new merch I
think that's a good China yeah we can
sell 300 of these Oh try 5,000
Hyundai Kona eBay let's say no he might
be supported for his end of life of
tamil one well comma one never existed
so never yeah 2016 was the end of life
what is this temp limitations on the
stock eon don't get it too hot it's
happy when people are happy no discord
that's amadhatter i you should go check
it out
let his end of life a panda Neos soap
and a neon are no longer you want to
what do I have to do it who wants to do
the recap
[Music]
business connections its back down they
make LTE modem
[Music]
just tuned in alright you want to recap
go to comma dot ai and leave the website
go recap
ah my recap is cheap yes yes you can use
your currently installed harness for the
comet to it to say oh the comma business
card yeah you'll remember it bro
just take a comma and just think a I go
the new mounts am i a celebrity I am
famous people have said that about me
yes look at these new mounts big GoPro
quick recap all right so we're kind of
AI we developed software called open
pilot open I can't say driving uh
controlling your car in limited
scenarios with a lot of legal
disclaimers but it's actually really
good our slogans make driving chill if
you want to make driving show you can
buy a comment to this to come back to
this is our new hardware it's beautiful
it's got a big screen a big beautiful
screen it's got an infrared camera which
is watching you
you can junction with these IR LEDs to
make sure you pay attention it's got a
custom engineered fan and heatsink
solution they buy some company in China
but it's truly good it's got four wires
so we can measure the fan speed dead
silent can't hear it and it has a built
in panda has a built in black panda act
like it's black because the case is
black built in black pants called the
Muto stuff for cancer and tears
it's got battery replacement circuitry
and unless an antenna right here in the
mountain s
thirty hours of no drive-in yep oh it's
designed to live in Cooper it's designed
to live in your car when radar control
sensitivity be reduced yeah we'll fix
that there's someone we already fixed
that internally all right if I see
anything else any other questions people
rename the uno two dos for historical
reasons its people no although that
would make a lot of sense we're not
working on flex ray you can't get a free
comet - what's the focus of 2020
end-to-end longitudinal and stability
stability stability stability and growth
and profitability so make sure to buy
them you recently bought an e on if it's
under 30 days you can return it just a
package it all back up nicely set
everything back we'll give you your
money back and then buy a comment so you
get a better 3d printer these are pretty
nice you think you're gonna like we
think you're gonna like them we've so we
did a bunch of things to improve our 3d
printers we put them in a big enclosure
alternative uses for old yawns yawns
make great door stops yawns make great
gifts for your cousin's who you kind of
feel like this about eons can be taken
apart and used as a 2016 era smartphone
well I'm really I'm really savage on the
Aeons now wow yeah now it's best pretty
savage like if I was like a real company
and someone gave me like like if I used
about how I'm supposed to talking
through the are things I'd never say
that like honestly I don't know why
you'd wanted to yawn by comment okay
does it have wireless charging no it's
just a battery oh did you drive here
Molly yeah three three months of comma
Prime the included that's a $72 value
what do you get why you get with common
crime a lot of good stuff you get one
year of drive storage you get remote
access to your car
anywhere you can if I had my phone in my
pocket I could show you we can take
pictures of the cars anywhere that's a
great new common products you're talking
to check your battery voltage watch your
dog in South America yeah I'm a prime
she'll Vil yeah if you want to purchase
common prime how do you do that you
already have your credit card on file
because that's how you activate we're
just gonna automatically bill you
connect app download the copper connect
app right now it's on the Play Store
it's on the App Store it's common five
available in Canada only without a SIM
cards you'd have to get your own is it
legal in North Korea
they'll have to ask Kim Jong hoon how to
connect to GM you'll have to ask B
tasarov if he's still around maybe Kim
jong-eun no comma to is an appreciating
asset absolutely this is no this is the
introductory price you guys know when I
say prices only go up I don't lie do we
ship to Europe yes we ship worldwide $30
flat rate you're responsible for all
custom fees because I'm not your
government on impasse those fees what
type of smartphone is use don't worry
about that you'll never think of it as a
smartphone it's fairly costume yeah USB
to obd2 buy a panda old sweep and a
white one it's just the North Koreans
called combi - yeah all right can we use
the same artist that Yan absolutely yeah
it's the same artist in the black panda
so if you already bought a black panda
is half of that money you can just reuse
and save that on the compet to come to
monitor your words it sparked what do
you mean by monitor you can get pictures
on your phone to come on
to be a veggie boss long you got to do
it yourself can I install the Aeons in
Europe for free uh yeah I don't control
yo you can do whatever you want for free
for whatever price you're denied your
device you do you want for it Brazil
yeah how fast we ship out everything
else I can ship on the 13th how much is
your gonna ship on the 20th it's more
advanced to the galaxy s 11 I don't know
about that in the commentary yo dole
wall drive it I think that's a good end
of question question Donna will give him
a few more minutes out you seem like
you're in the rise look we still have
like three hundred forty two people here
we can't let him down guys if all 342
are you bought no retweet on the twos
right now did I try the Honda bond we've
had pong oh they like your rings common
crime is not available in Europe it is
but you have to get your own SIM card
this is a kid to twitch my Michelle like
it really is I show for all things prime
does it have a JTAG court know how many
have been sold a lot wise Alex in a rush
[Music]
I stuffed my face at the Aria buffet
last I was pushing like my stomach was
out to here guys not even exaggerating I
think it is too but costs like 50 more
dollars
the only the Aria buffet had oysters I
was happy with the oysters the sushi was
really bad the pokeball was good
what press tried it we did Roadshow and
VentureBeat this morning
what hotel we're staying we got a condo
we got the Vegas office of comedy night
the new model of Trent after thank you
thank you
common or mobile I trifocal will
consider you can't buy a bubble I Drive
boat because globalized windows Tesla's
Apple and we are I lost money gambling
last night what I'm going to talk about
but Nick made money and now it's made
money so everybody made money oh I bet
the don't pass line it's the best odds
in the casino and the table hates me if
the iana comment to have the same
hardware why wouldn't you be phased out
before the competition if you have any
on with a black panda it won't be if you
haven't gone with a white panda the
problem is you don't have the the GPS
the thermal solution in the combi 2 is
also a lot better 0-8 probably will be
supported I make no promises about the
future the only thing I will say is that
the combi 2 will definitely support
version 1.0 can I switch the camera yeah
but they like
[Music]
you have our community videos you guys
have good videos post them on the Gaspar
video channel you have a few days a mare
teams just working
SiC chargesheeted applause so many
supported cars right now dory we didn't
forget you community maintain and
butters what's expected 1.0 stability
stability stability
Janee the developer harness for kia
right now yes and if every one of them
just bought a comet Oh seventy three
hundred forty four thousand dollars we
can buy a house oh one more reminder
about affirm oh yeah if you guys are
like wow that's a really high price you
should feel like a good American and
spend to be in debt with a firm look
don't get in debt you guys I trust
you're smart enough to make your own
decisions we did offer a firm we do
offer a firm if you'd like to buy with a
firm you can pay monthly yeah but I feel
bad shilling for this does not want
people spending and down the glacier you
got me in debt for your shit that's your
choice Ben you got to make your own
choices
that's about freedom that's about being
an adult I need to start shelling for
Defense College hands just purchase
common to without a harness know if you
already have the old martes it's exactly
the same um this is an appreciating
asset I wouldn't really focus on it as
an investment but we do raise the prices
so like if your choice is like if you're
gonna buy it and thinking you're gonna
sell it for more later yeah probably not
but if you're gonna buy it now because
you know it's gonna cost more money
later yeah that's a good idea because
it's gonna cost more money later so
those of us have any late can you have a
recap this is a comma to so over there
you should buy one at our website
comment on AI check out our new website
kind of new website we have install
videos it's all easy Fatlip in
what I got some funny ones home talking
through the party like my name is on the
bedtime in Europe all right
would I host test drives if you're
famous or you have a large outlet is the
driver cam customer off-the-shelf it's
custom we have them made at a camera
factory in China Yan with white panda
will get dropped soon yeah gray panda a
little bit longer I think white pant is
gonna get dropped in 0-8 who we ship the
localizer a great pant is gonna last a
little bit longer
black Panda + E on should last a long
time the only problem is the driver
monitoring so we're gonna see we're
gonna see if this becomes a problem you
know a few people have fallen asleep and
we really want to prevent that and
that's one of the reasons we're really
excited about the ah the driver
monitoring operating both day and night
yes shout out to Asia we made Black
Manta plus e on what white definitely
won't support him young be made with a
remote screen no remote screen test
drive me I'm as famous as you if you
come if you have like a channel if you
like a channel you want to post
something on we could never do it
we were for supper updates I can't force
anything on you
what does open pilot what oh we lose
them to connect internet time we know
it's gonna be 30 days I know you guys
complain what does open pilot have the
autopilot does it what does linux have
that mac OS to us it don't compare us to
that compare install the less to which
is what all the other cars are running
kona electric if you make it support
that i don't know anything about iran
driver monitor yes very important very
important
you dumped test the autopilot what does
that mean how do you test about it isn't
it just like you're talking about spring
you chose to share this heavy frame
oh we don't have any you know I did
measure the comma - if it's a sec sauce
it's six and a half basically inches
wide it's the same size except the
stupid mount isn't up here it's back
here it's a stealth mount the mounts
completely invisible when you see in the
car it's great in the car yeah do we
ship to Iran I don't know we learned
that we can't ship wide ours I don't
think we shipped to our round sorry no
we can ship light ours but I don't think
we ship - I'm sorry about that insurance
companies offering a discount for usage
but they don't seem to be upset if you
are using it so that's good how do you
get driving data people don't know opt
into prime Wi-Fi
I see more tired than usual I'm sick
guys I've had a cold for the last week
prerequisite to install an e on a brain
ah fitness fitness stack that's what I'm
talking about by comma twos oh you will
love large GoPro the new standard large
GoPro it's great on your windshield you
love your black man except if you love
your black man to set up keep it if you
can't want to keep your existing
insurance provider keep it and I meet it
we ship to Africa sure unless you're
like on one of the like export control
countries they're just somewhere nice
like Ethiopia will ship to you look at
you GOP laughs yeah we got custom cover
drops suits
show the back doors gonna model their
job
FES you will need to delete tesla
Tesla's not our competition our
competition is legacy automakers sorry
why it's coming summer it's a lot faster
now queue logs and cucumbers making a
lot faster it's common insurance coming
insurance is boring guys I woke up one
day and I'm like George do you really
want to make an insurance company and
the answer was no oh there's no switches
there's no switches on the harness and
there's definitely no switches on the
comet tail Elon shouted us out whoo I'm
how its functionality different offline
versus online offline you get updates
you get dashcam being sent back to the
cloud one year of storage now if you
have come a prime stealth murdered a
stealth mount that's right
one woman localized reprove 0-8 I know
the bitrate slow well that's the
trade-off you want fast or do you want
quality
let's pick three jumpsuit in order 300
yeah if 300 still happens it comes
around again what is the comment still
one plus it's based on a leaky Cola pro
three but it's fairly custom to help
like open the phone up we take the
battery out should we replace the camera
can you get a broken Tama for research
you can buy a comma and then break it
and then you can do research on it yeah
they all work you want quality well you
can get quality just probably explore
any I fired the exploring cabana guys
and wasn't getting the past hour so it's
never gonna get better now it is open
source wide replace the camera because
it's infrared it can see in the dark at
night just like in that Paramore song
about castles even in the dark as IR
yeah driver monitoring is you can't turn
it off anymore we've turned that off a
while ago did you ever do Hardware
swapping no come on we're a small
company guys why you think I'm dealing
with that I think I'm dealing with like
seventeen miss shape and packages that
we're gonna like put some come on what
do I think about all the MLA six I think
they're overhyped it's only the front
camera place you have the back camera
saying ah is BMW five no we'll use
something like that in the comma three
comma two just came out we're not even
thinking about future products yet when
it's gonna happen what a pre-orders get
personal voicing for me will shout you
out if you buy it right now
am I gonna be the AVN's if someone
invites me absolutely up down let's do
it
the self-driving work offline yeah you
don't need internet connection
you don't need internet connection it
has a check you have to connect every 30
days it used to be seven but it's not a
big deal it totally works offline gonna
have to compile comment
in the 2020 Civic Nebraskan how good it
is tell me to dance really good
nada go to DEFCON any more boys more
chips in the counter - it's a Snapdragon
820 one what phone is it inside it's
based on parts of a lake oh all right
just in New York and that's why I got
sick what are the main goals for twenty
end-to-end longitudinal canceling your
own order just reach in to support will
cancel it feel free to place a comma -
you know what's with the Sony lanyard
Sony has too much money and they waited
on that you need to partner with a
rental car company and my partner with
anybody rental car companies to lock the
bottom and put them in the car what's
new the comma - its brand new it came
out today go buy one look at adding
voice control cool
you won't comment to me well you're
gonna have to wait till at least a while
it's porn until the Nvidia Jetson give a
try it's what's better about this one
it's free the website we can't just keep
doing recaps it's gonna get weird it's
gonna some people have been here a long
time they want new fresh original
content auto resume supported bro if I
knew things like that off the top of my
head no we're not level four we're level
- we're proud level to be proud level to
proud levels - why such a slow chip
chips plenty fast guys my tech civic
stuff is so slow to accelerate if you
need car it's pretty fast what's your
email George at comedy I will your
wheelchair support it that's why it's
open-source your PIN tweet is still car
horn so we got to change that oh we got
to change up in three days
image oh nice did comma already sell
lighters on ebay no we haven't sold them
yet
Volvo's in our booth right now maybe
they wanna buy some light off um where
did Sony's CAD currently in the TV
market I don't know everyone the
livestream I like that recap the recaps
alright yeah so there were recaps what's
the longest trip made without
interruptions who knows we did check in
our data I think it's probably something
like four hours might even be longer at
least if you ordered the car odors in
the last 30 days can you get a 200 our
refund well if you order anything within
the last 30 days you can send it back it
hasn't even shipped it hasn't shipped
our lines are better tar lines better
the super combo model why is there a
weather vane behind these they make
weather vane wait what happened
oh yeah yeah yeah and they're like how
do you doing this how good do they want
to buy some data also update amazing
I'll sell your data guys we should have
like yeah we didn't but that
will sell you you want to buy some data
are we still honoring Aeon warranties
yeah the TVs are not playing for Cabana
I know what's a release date for the
comma three yo that's like comma two
misspelled it that's like saying like yo
but I want the iPhone 12 where's the
iPhone 12 coming out I bought an iPhone
11 you should buy a comma - alright
okay I think that's the stream guys
thank you all for being with us on this
incredible journey where you're here a
you should buy stuff so we can continue
this incredible journey by comma twos
tell your friends to buy comma twos
you're gonna love it it's really a great
product if you could download a comma -
we would love to make that possible link
you pre-order you can order right now
it's not really a pre-order it ships on
the 20th if you're in within the first
300 we already have the made we just
need to do some final tests on them want
to make sure that your comment - works
great we're putting them through a big
QA thing I did not good comm I'm still
right here thank you all for joining how
many sold we're gonna keep that a secret
from here on out but I will say it's at
least 20 if you want to invest in the
company you can't because it's private
and you can blame the SEC I would love
to make it possible but all plug lay is
to follow me on instagram at george hotz
that's right that's right
keep up the great work thank you thank
you very much it's nice having you all
here today and you'll see us from seat
yes we don't map shit cuz you don't need
Maps you just need eyes alright okay